This is a work of fiction.
Any resemblance to real persons, groups or events is purely coincidental.
This is Oreki.
折木です
Hello, it's Chitanda speaking. Sorry for bothering you during the break.
もしもし　千反田です
お休みのところすみません
おお
Would you happen to have any plans for the day after tomorrow?
突然ですが　明後日何かご予定はありますか
Nope...
いや
Thank God!
よかった
Um, Oreki...
あの　折木さん　いきなりでご迷惑なのは重々承知なんですが
I know that this is asking a lot of you,
but could you please carry the umbrella?
どうか傘を持ってくれませんか
Carry... the umbrella?
傘を　持つ
Yes.
そうです
I don't really follow.
よくわからんのだが
Sorry, I didn't explain it properly.
すみません　説明が下手で
The thing is, we're having a Hina festival at the shrine near my house.
ええと　要するにですね
私の家の近くの神社で雛祭りをやるんです
Hina festival?
雛祭り　もう四月だぞ
It's already April!
It's held according to the lunar calendar.
旧暦合わせなんです
Actually, one of the umbrella holders for the dolls had an accident,
実はお雛さまに傘を差す役が急に怪我をしまして
and there's no one else who can wear the costume.
代わりにその衣装を着られそうな人がいないんです
I think the size should fit you.
折木さんなら　サイズが合いそうなんですが
Wait a moment. Someone has to hold the umbrella?
待て　人間が傘を持つのか
Yes.
はい　どうか力を貸してもらえませんか
Could you please help us?
Okay, I'll be there.
分かった　行くよ
本当ですか　ありがとうございます
Really?
Thank you so much!
I just have to stand there, right?
横で立ってればいいんだろう
No, you need to walk too.
いいえ　一緒に歩いてもらいます
Walk? With a doll?
歩くって　雛と
Yes. That's right.
はい　そうです
The dolls walk?
雛が歩くのか
Yes.
はい
How?
何で雛が
Oreki!
折木さん　あんまり雛雛と言わないでください
Could you stop saying "dolls" all the time?
It's a bit embarrassing...
私だって少しは恥ずかしいんですから
Don't tell me...
まさか　雛って
Yes, at the Mizunashi Shrine's living Hina festival, girls take on the dolls' roles.
はい　水梨神社の生き雛祭りは女の子が生き雛になるんです
Ah.
I've played the Hina doll for a few years now.
お雛様の役はここ数年私が仰せつかっています
Mizunashi Shrine
The usual slope
|
v
follow the little
<- river upstream
just follow the road
^
|
cross the Choukyuu bridge
^
|
cherry trees (one of them is
blooming out of season)
"Follow the little river upstream,
小川沿いに上流へ
then cross the Choukyuu bridge after the cherry trees."
桜の先に長久橋
@ 湮·Molly／小然·酸菜／喵儿·小冷／时末·竭力而为
KamiGami
Today is a real mess, but I get over it with a sigh
複雑に構えた今日が 息を呑んで澄ましてる
You get the idea, right?
身に覚えあるだろう 君はどうしたい
What do you wanna do?
You act as if nothing happened
何もなかったそぶりで  かばう痛みはもう
As if your heart didn't ache
It almost feels encouraging,
心強いくらいに 急かすんだ
the way you're rushing me
Hold it and let it overflow
掴んでこぼして 不完全な僕たちが
We're all imperfect
光って見えない 未来の自分を創れるなら
I can't see it well in the light,
but if we can change our future selves
目覚めるまま走れ 蜃気楼を追い越して
Wake up and run
Go and surpass the mirage
変わりたいまま走れ 自由な違和感で
Try to change and run
with the discomfort of freedom
届きそうな輝きと今を選んでいこう
We can reach that shining light
Follow it into the present
Don't hesitate to act
飛びたつ手を知らない
Deep or quick, just keep breathing
深い 浅い 呼吸を重ねて
Hyouka
Dolls in the Distance
绕远的偶人
Ah, is that the cherry tree blooming out of season?
あれか　狂い咲きの桜
Chitanda didn't know they were fixing the bridge?
千反田は工事のことを知らなかったのか
すみません　ここを通っていいですか
Excuse me, can I cross?
はぁ　いいぞ
Sure, go on.
これから仕事始めるから　もう通れなくなるよ
We'll start work soon, and the bridge will be closed after that.
はい
Excuse me!
すいません
Hey, I've brought it.
花井さん　持ってきました
Ah, just put it down in the hall.
お―　広間で頼むわ
ウェス
Sure.
あのう
Um...
Who're you?
あんたは
I'm Oreki. I've been asked to hold the umbrella.
折木と言います
傘持ちを頼まれて来たんですが
ふうん
千反田から聞いていませんか
Didn't Chitanda tell you?
She asked me to help out by holding the umbrella.
傘を持つ人の代役に来たんです
ああ　羽沢のとこの代わりか
Ah, instead of the Hazawa kid?
いやあすまなかった　さあ　上がって
Sorry, sorry. Just come in.
Say, who's taking care of the booze?
花井さん　酒の手配は誰がやっとる
I asked Nakatake to do it.
酒なら中竹さんに任せとる
中竹さん　大丈夫か
Nakatake, is it gonna be all right?
Sure, everything's going well.
頼んでやる
And what about that thing during the day?
それより　昼のあれがどうなった
I asked the women to handle it.
女衆に頼んだぞ
I see...
確かか
Hey, where are the lanterns?
おい　幟の予備は
In the hall.
広間です
I see. I'll take a look.
そっか　じゃあ見てみる
Oreki!
折木さん
Yes?
はい
君は千反田さんの娘さんに傘を差す人だね
You'll be holding the umbrella for the Chitanda girl, right?
Yes.
そう聞いてます
花井さん　電話　新聞社から
Mr Hanai, phone call!
It's from the newspaper!
ええ　まっちゃく
Oh, jeez.
どうも落ち着かん
I just can't get a moment's rest...
Nakatake!
中竹
Where's the booze?
お前　酒はどうした
It'll be here by one.
一時には届きます
You idiot!
馬鹿野郎
The procession gets back at half past twelve!
行列が戻るのは十二時半
Does one pm sound like it'll be on time to you?!
一時に届いて間に合うか
Make them hurry!
早めでもらえ
すぐに
Right away.
まったく
For crying out loud.
Ah!
お―
Yes?
はい
You're the guy Chitanda asked to help?
あんたが　千反田さんに頼まれたお人か
Yes. My name is Oreki.
はい　折木と言います
Sorry for asking you to come out all this way.
それは遠いところすまんことです
どうも人手が足りんで
We're short on people, so we really need your help.
余所の人にまで迷惑をかけて申し訳ない
I'd greatly appreciate your assistance today.
今日はどうぞよろしく頼みます
こちらこそ　余所者が交じったようですみません
I'm sorry to barge in as an outsider.
邪魔にならないようにさせてもらいます
I'll do my best not to get in the way.
If there's anything I can do to help, please let me know.
行き届かないことがあったら教えてください
You're a good boy.
しっかりしていなさん
生まれて初めて言われた
First time in my life anyone's told me that.
Oreki, was it?
折木さんでしたな
出番までゆっくりしていなさい
Please take it easy.
ああ
吹屋さん　氏子総代は
Mr. Fukiya, have the worshippers' representatives arrived?
揃っとる
All here.
The children in the procession?
稚児は
揃っとる
All here.
生き雛は
The living dolls?
後すこしだ
Just a little longer.
よーし
Okay.
Tanimoto, will the Choukyuu bridge be all right?
谷本　長久橋は大丈夫か
I asked Mr. Murai to do something about it.
村井先生にお願いしてあります
で　工事は止めてもらえるんだな
So we can get them to delay the work, right?
Yes.
はい　任せておけと言われました　はい
He told me to leave it to him.
They've already started work on the Choukyuu bridge.
長久橋なら　工事を始めてましたよ
何
What?
何だと
Tanimoto, you made sure, right?!
谷本　お前確認したんだろうな
I asked Mr. Murai!
村井先生には念を押しましたよ
折木さん
Oreki,
間違いないのかい
are you sure about this?
Yes...
はい
園君
Sono!
はい
Yes?
すまんが　軽トラ出して確認に行ってくれ
Take my truck and check.
Roger.
はい
Tanimoto!
谷本君
はい
Yes?
村井君に　いや　中川工務店に電話しなさい
Call Murai... No, call Nakagawa Construction.
Roger.
はい
This should do, right, Hanai?
これでいいかな　花井君
はい
Yes...
Is something wrong?
何かまずいんですか
The procession is supposed to cross the Choukyuu bridge.
行列が長久橋を渡るんだ
Oh.
は
君の勘違いならいいんだがな
Are you sure you're not mistaken?
なぜ俺を睨む
Why are you staring at me like that?
It's true! They've already begun work!
本当だ　工事が始まってるぞ
Tanimoto, what the hell have you been doing?!
谷本　だからお前は
I-It doesn't make any sense!
い　いや　それがおかしいんです
Mr. Murai contacted the construction company!
工務店には確かに村井先生から連絡が行ってるんです
He asked them to put the work off until tomorrow.
今日は工事を止めるように
Then why haven't they?!
なら　何で
Someone called them two days ago to say the work could go ahead.
ところが　一昨日やっぱり予定通り進めていいと
電話はあったそうです
Who did that?
誰から
それが
They didn't name themselves.
はっきり名乗らなかったそうで
I heard that too.
作業員も同じことを言ってます
We've got more important matters to deal with.
原因はいい　それより　今は対応だ
何とか工事を止めてもらうわけには行かんのか
Can't we ask them to stop the work?
It's too late.
もう　手遅れだ
The TV crew's here already. What if there was an accident?
テレビも来とるし
何かの間違いで怪我人が出たらどうする
どう回るかを考えた方がいい
同じルートを往復しますか
Why don't they follow the same route back?
They could just walk down the east bank of the river then back the same way.
こう　川の東側を行って帰って
The people on the east bank will appreciate that, but what about the west?
東はそれでもいいかもしれんが
西はどうする
生き雛無しか
No doll parade for them?
そうだ
Then how about walking down to the Choukyuu bridge,
なら　一旦長久橋まで行って
doubling back, then doing the same on the other side?
戻って　西側の道を
We can't make the procession walk the whole distance twice.
行列を倍も歩かせるのは無理だ
だったら　橋の中間まで行って
Then what if we walk half way, then come back and do the same on the west side?
折り返して　西側の
How could we do something so half-assed in front of the cameras?
テレビの前でそんないい加減なことできるか
Then what can we do?
じゃ　どう折衷んです
Why don't we walk down to the Tooji bridge?
遠路橋まで下る手があります
If we go as far as the Tooji bridge
遠路橋を渡って　茅橋まで戻ってくれば
then come back on the Kaya bridge,
it'll be just a bit longer than the original route.
元のルートよりちょっと長くなるだけで済みます
遠路橋か
The Tooji bridge, huh?
ちょっとなあ
I don't know...
あのう
Um, is Mr. Oreki here?
折木さんとおっしゃる方はいますかね
Yes, how can I help?
はい　何でしょう
千反田さんの娘さんが呼んでます
Mr. Chitanda's daughter is looking for you.
何の用だ
What does she want?
Who knows...
さあ
Living
dolls
Make-up
and
dressing
room
折木さんですね
Are you Oreki?
Yes...
お　ああ
Sorry for calling you this way, but I'm still in the middle of getting my make-up done.
すみません　こんな形で
着付けの途中なものですから
That's Chitanda... isn't it?
千反田　だよなあ
I sent for you because I heard there was some trouble.
お呼びしたのは他でもありません
何かトラブルがあったようですね
ああ
Yeah.
Is it serious?
重大なことですか
Seems so.
みたいだ
I see.
そうですか
では何かあったのか話してください
Please tell me what happened.
もうあまり時間がありません
We don't have much time.
The Choukyuu bridge...
長久橋という橋で…
So someone suggested a route that crossed the Tooji bridge instead,
それで　遠路橋を通るルートが提案されたんだが
but then everyone...
それを聞いた皆は…
Are you listening?
聞いてるか
聞いています
I am.
But then everyone looked as though that was the worst option possible.
それを聞いた皆はなぜか気まずそうな顔でためらっている
That's it.
以上だ
You've summed it up well.
大変よくまとまったお話でした
どうも
Thanks.
Oreki, could I trouble you to deliver a message?
折木さん　伝言をお願いできますか
Sure...
ああ
I'll talk to the priests leading the procession.
先方の宮司には私から話をします
I'll ask my father to call the worshippers' representatives.
氏子総代には父から電話をするよう頼んでみます
Please tell them that.
そうお伝えください
それだけでいいのか
That's all?
They should understand.
それだけで分かるはずです
That's what she told me.
という話なんですが
Okay then, that's that.
じゃあ　頼もうか
Everyone, we're crossing the Tooji bridge.
よし皆　道は遠路橋周りだ
What are you doing?!
何しとる
Hurry up and get to work!
さっさと支度せんか
春分
太阳行至词 日夜平分之时也
Spring Equinox
As the Sun crosses the middle of the heavens,
the day and the night are equal.
Hyouka
あの　この役あなたじゃ無理なんですか
Couldn't you play this role?
The costume doesn't fit me.
衣装のサイズが合わないよ
That's true.
まあ　確かに
This procession's a once-in-a-lifetime sight. I came all the way home just to see it.
それに　めったに見られん行列だから
わざわざ帰省してきたんだ
役になったら見物できない
And I couldn't do that if I had to take part in it.
That's true.
さいですか
これでよし
Done.
さあ　どうだ
How is it?
似合わんな
It doesn't really fit you.
I must agree.
同感です
The 62nd Kamiyama Living Doll Festival
It's freezing.
寒っ
Is that... Irisu?
あれは　入須先輩
Damn.
しまった
This is bad. This is really bad.
よくない
これはよくない
多分　なんとしても　俺はここに来るべきではなかった
I definitely shouldn't have come here.
My low-energy lifestyle is in mortal danger.
俺の省エネ主義が致命的に脅かされている
I can't see Chitanda...
千反田が見えない
I can't stop thinking about it.
気になる　気になる
I can't stop thinking about it!
What if I caught a glimpse of Chitanda's face,
もし今紅をさし　目を伏せている千反田を正面から見られたら
taking in the makeup on her skin and her eyes, cast modestly downward...
それはどんなにか
Houtarou!
奉太郎
いや　素晴らしかった
That was great!
Chitanda and Irisu looked amazing!
千反田さんと入須先輩の気品ったら　なかったよ
本当素敵だったよねぇ
Yeah, it was so pretty!
それで　千反田さんたちは？
Where are they now?
In the main hall.
本殿だ　穢れを払うんだと
They're purging impurities.
Oh?
ちなみに　奉太郎はちっとも似合ってなかったよ
By the way, that outfit really didn't suit you.
Cut it out.
ほっとけ
本当　台無しだったわ
You were such a waste for that role.
言いたい放題だな
I don't recall asking for criticism.
I'll go get another one of these.
これ　もう一本買ってくるよ
Oreki, thanks...
折木　ありがとうね
For what?
何がだ
バレンタインの件　なかなか言う機会なかったから
For what you did at Valentine's. I hadn't had an opportunity to thank you yet.
ああ　どうだ　その後
How did it go?
It's going.
まあ　それなりに
I see.
そうか
I blew my top too.
俺も葛藤なってな　珍しくあいつに突っかかった
Almost ended up punching him.
I heard.
うん　聞いた
あ　入須先輩
Irisu!
Ah, Oreki.
いや　折木君
お雛だったんですね
You were one of the dolls, right?
It's a long story.
色々あってな
そういえば　長久橋の話聞いたぞ
By the way, I heard about the Choukyuu bridge.
There are a bunch of things that don't make sense.
色々と合点のいかないことがあるようだが
What do you think?
君はどう思う
Hmm...
あ　どうでしょうね　分かりません
I wonder. Who knows?
I see.
そうか　君なら謎を解いて見せてくれると思ったのだが
I hoped you'd be able to solve this mystery.
Stop it, please.
やめてください
折木君
Oreki.
Huh?
あのとき私には役目があった
I played my part back then.
This time I'm just a doll.
でも　今日はただのお雛だ
Today, you'll see only the real me.
こんな気楽な身から虚言は出ないよ
Okay...
はあ
折木さん
Oreki...
Oreki!
折木さん
Wh-What?
なん　なんだ？
Today was so hard! I had to put up with it the whole time!
今日は大変でした
ずっと　ずっと我慢してました
Ah, having to play a doll? Must've been tough.
ああ　生雛な　お疲れ
Not that!
違います　長久橋です　中川工務店さんのことです
The Choukyuu bridge! The incident with Nakagawa Construction!
Ah, that...
そっちか
I wanted to figure it out, but I was too preoccupied with my role for the procession.
色々考えました
でも　役目があるからぐっと堪えました
だけど　聞きたくて聞きたくて　つまり
But I wanted to ask you so much! I—
Let me guess. You can't stop thinking about it.
私　気になります
Exactly! You've noticed lots of clues, right?
そうです
折木さん　実は色々気付いているんでしょ？
I've got a vague idea.
まあ　一人心当たりはある
Me too!
私もです
どうでしょう　何かに書いて　一斉に見せ合うというのは
How about we write it all down and look at everything together?
Sure, but what do we have to write on?
別にいいが　何に書く？
はい
いいですか　では　せーの
Ready? One, two!
The brown-haired guy
Konari's son
小成さんの息子さんは髪が茶色です
Konari's son is brown-haired.
ふたりとも同じやつか
So we suspect the same guy?
Yes. Why did you think of him?
ええ　なぜそう考えたんですか
First, we know for sure that someone called to tell them to go ahead with the bridge repairs.
まず　今日は工事していいって電話があったのは間違いになさそうだな
はい　そう思います
Yes, I agree.
So, who would have done that?
なら　その電話を誰がかけたかだ
Everyone was in a rush today,
今日はみんな混乱してたが
and only one person acted on the premise that the Choukyuu bridge would be closed.
ただ一人長久橋が通れないことを前提に行動してるやつがいた
And that would be Konari's son, right?
それが小成さんの息子さんだと
Yeah. I talked to him when I was changing.
ああ　着付けのときに話したんだ
あの茶髪は
He said the procession was a "once-in-a-lifetime sight".
「めったに見られん行列を見るためにわざわざ帰省してきた」と言ってた
Did he?
そうでしたか
でも　おかしいだろう
But that doesn't make sense. This festival is held every year.
祭りは毎年やってるんだから
It's not something a local would call "once-in-a-lifetime".
地元の人間がめったに見られないってことじゃない
You're right, that is a little strange.
確かに少し変ですね
But this year, it really was a once-in-a-lifetime sight.
ところが　今年はめったに見られないことが起きた
Do you know why?
何だと思う？
The route was changed,
ルートが変更になりましたね
so we had to cross the Tooji br—
それで　長久橋を回っ…
Ah, the cherry tree!
あっ　桜！
Yeah, the cherry tree that was blooming out of season.
そう　狂い咲きの桜だ
The only way you can see it is via today's route.
今日のルートだけでしか見られないんだ
生き雛が桜の下を通るって光景は
Seeing the living dolls pass under a blooming cherry tree
really would be the sight of a lifetime.
これぞめったに見られない行列だ
Was it all just for that?
そんなことのために
そうでもないさ
I wouldn't say "just".
折木さん
Oreki?
Anyway, why did you think it was him?
それより　お前はどうしてあいつだと思ったんだ
Well, I guess...
それは　その…
He was the only one I could think of who'd be able to
いろんな人の面子を潰して平気でいられる人が
keep his cool after causing so much trouble for so many people.
小成さんの息子さんしか思いつかなかったからです
I see...
なるほど
But after hearing your explanation, now I'm certain.
でも　折木さんの話を聞いて納得しました
What do you mean?
というと
小成さんの息子さんは写真家になるのが夢なんだそうです
It's his dream to become a photographer.
He's attending a technical school in Osaka for that.
そのために　大阪の専門学校に通っています
ああ　それで
Ah, I get it.
He must've wanted to take pictures of that rare sight.
きっと珍しい景色が撮りたかったんでしょうね
Well, then...
さあってな
折木さん　あの部屋で私　宮司に連絡すると言いましたよね
Oreki, I said in the dressing room that I was going to call the head priests, right?
ああ　それで混乱はぴったりと収まった
Yeah, and the chaos calmed down instantly.
This isn't much of a story, but please listen.
つまらないかもしれませんが　聞いてください
ああ
Sure.
Do Not Cross
Nakagawa Constructions
Long ago, this area was divided into the north and south.
昔　このあたりは南北に分かれていました
Our village was to the north, and another village was to the south.
北が私たちの村　南が別の村で
Choukyuu
Bridge
There were fights over land and water.
土地争いも水争いもあったようです
That's long since past, but at religious events like this,
それももう昔の話ですが
ああいう神事の際に無断で入るのは今でも揉め事の種です
crossing over into their land can still spark conflict.
Ah, I see.
ああ　それでか
We need to give advance notice,
事前に一報したい
but only a few people have the means to do that.
でも　そういうチャンネルがある人はあまりいないんです
That's where you come in?
そこでお前の出番か
If I let the people of the south know, we can pass through their land with no issues.
私が向こうに連絡すれば　皆さん安心して南に入れますから
なるほど　里志が名家と呼ぶわけだ
I see. Satoshi was right to call your family powerful.
そうでしょうか
I wonder.
This world is so tiny.
小さな世界じゃないですか　神山市の北
All I did was smooth over a problem
小さな町の北と南の調整をしただけです
between the north and south halves of a small town north of Kamiyama city.
Of course, I'm not saying what I did was totally insignificant,
もちろん　取るに足らないことだとは思いません
but I don't think it's anything major either.
でも　大きなことだとも思わないんです
I guess... that might be true.
そうかも…しれんな
Even if I go to college, I'll return here one day.
無事大学に進学しても　私はここに戻ってきます
Wherever I may roam, I'll end up coming back here.
どんなルートを辿っても　私の終着点はここ
ここなんです
Oreki, what did you decide to major in from second year onward?
折木さん　二年からの文理選択どうしました？
I chose arts.
ああ　文系にした
I chose science.
私は理系にしました
そうか
I see.
I don't mind coming back here, nor do I find it sad.
私はここに戻ることを嫌だとも悲しいとも思っていません
I want to fulfill my duty as the daughter of the Chitanda family.
千反田の娘として　相応の役割を果たしたいと思っています
I've been thinking all this time of a means by which I could do that.
そのための方法をずっと考えていました
A means, huh?
方法… ね
There are two that I can think of.
ふたつあると思います
ひとつは商品価値の高い作物を作ることで皆で豊かになる方法
One would be gaining wealth for everyone by producing high-value crops.
The other would be optimizing production by management so that no one will end up worse than they are now.
もうひとつは経営的戦略眼で生産を効率化し
皆で貧しくならない方法
私は結局前者を選ぶことにしました
In the end, I chose the former.
That's why you chose science?
そのための理系選択か
はい
Yes.
Yeah, I'd say the latter wouldn't really fit you.
確かにあとの方はあまりお前に向いてない気がする
During the culture fair, I caused so much trouble for everyone that it made me realize.
文化祭のとき　皆さんにさんざんお手数をおかけして分かりました
I'm probably not fit for managing a company.
私　多分会社経営には向いていません
Yeah, I guess that's right.
そうだな
そう思う
Please look, Oreki.
見てください　折木さん
ここが私の場所です
This is my place.
All we have is water and soil.
水と土しかありません
The people aren't getting any younger either.
人もだんだん老い疲れてきています
私はここを最高に美しいとは思いません
I don't think this place is the most beautiful ever,
nor do I see that many possibilities here.
可能性に満ちているとも思っていません
But...
でも　折木さんに紹介したかったんです
I wanted to show it to you.
ところで
Speaking of which...
That whole optimizing management idea you gave up on...
お前が諦めた経営的戦略眼についてだが
Why don't you leave that to me?
俺がおさめるというのはどうだろう
Speaking of what?
ところで　何ですか
Ah, um...
あ　いや
あのときの里志もこんな気持ちだったんだろうか
I guess this is how Satoshi felt back then.
It's gotten cold lately, hasn't it?
寒くなってきたな
No. It's already spring.
いいえ　もう春です
Choukyuu
Bridge
Do Not Cross
Nakagawa Constructions
诸神字幕组《冰果》BD到此完结 感谢各位的支持
更多中日双语作品 请关注www.kamigami.org!
The situation is unscientific
状況は非科学的に 感情のモンタージュ
A montage of emotions
Who's calling who?
誰が誰を呼んでる
You look away when our eyes are about to meet
振り向けば逃げてく視線（感じる）
I can feel it
Am I just imagining things? It's so cold of you
気のせいじゃつれないよ アンテナは才能って言うでしょ
It takes talent to read minds
You know
だって（だって） 知りたい（君は違うの？）
I wanna know
Don't you?
I'll fix the fire of youth in your heart while I can
青春の温度差 今のうち正してあげるよ
If we can do it today why leave it for tomorrow
明日解決するなら 今でもよくない？
I want to solve your mystery
君のミステリー解いてみたい
Look for the back of the boy, burdened with secrets
少年の秘密めいた背中探せ（今日も）
Even today
You are a fantasy and I'm drawn to you
君はファンタジー 惹かれてゆくよ（ずるい）
This growing curiosity
膨らんだ好奇心 とりたくはないのに
There's no twist in the story
I can't stop thinking about it
気になるよ 興味深い どうして
It's so interesting
But why?